

MD. Mohyminul Islam

Full Stack Web Developer / Python Expert

About Me

I am **MD. Mohyminul Islam.** I'm a professional **Full Stack Developer**. at Fiverr and Upwork. Since beginning my journey as a freelancer nearly 3+ years ago, I've completed 30+ projects for clients.

Technical fields that I worked with in my career: -HTML5 - CSS3 -SASS- Tailwind CSS- Bootstrap-JavaScript -jquery - Ajax -PHP- Python- JAVA- Git / GitHub- WordPress, Wix, etc.

My completed projects:- Woo Commerce Store Design, Personal/agency/Traveling/magazine/Blog Website, Increase website speed & SEO, Landing page etc.

Professional Experience

Itforwebs.com | Software Company

2022 - Present

Key Responsibilities:

- Founder
- · Web Developer

Fiverr / Upwork | Web Developer

Present

Key responsibilities:

- Professional Freelancer
- Web Design & Development

CricnNews.com | News Website

2020-2022

Key responsibilities:

- Programmer Manager
- · Senior Developer
- Content & SEO Expert

• Content & 350 Expe

Achievements

2022 -Present Volunteer at National Tech Carnival-2023

2022 - Present College Programming Competition-2022, 2nd Place Winner (Team-Leader)

My Contact

mohyminulislam2020@gmail.com

+880 1861720669

Birampur, Dinajpur

www.mohyminulislam.com

Skills

Html / CSS JavaScript Python

Bootstrap/Tailwind PHP MySQL

jQuery / Ajax Git / GitHub WordPress

Expert

- Programming
- Web Design
- Web Development
- WordPress Development

Education

Khulna Polytechnic Institute
 Computer Science and Engineering (CSE)
 2021-(Present)

Birampur Pilot High School

Secondary School Certificate
Completed in 2021

 FN SOFTWARES & INSTITUTE Web Web Development
 Completed in 2020

language

- English Fluent
- Bangla Native